invests.com 2016-10-03

# Privacy Policy - Invests.com Invests.com

**Privacy Policy**  
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the website located at www.invests.com (Invests.com) and Dot Com Investors Inc and governs data collection and usage. Invests.com is operated by Dot Com Investors Inc. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Dot Com Investors Inc include Invests.com. The Invests.com website is a News and Information site. By using the Invests.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
Dot Com Investors Inc may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Dot Com Investors Inc’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Dot Com Investors Inc may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender and household income. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Dot Com Investors Inc. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Dot Com Investors Inc website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Dot Com Investors Inc’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Dot Com Investors Inc encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Dot Com Investors Inc so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Dot Com Investors Inc is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Dot Com Investors Inc website.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
Dot Com Investors Inc collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.  
Dot Com Investors Inc may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Dot Com Investors Inc and its affiliates. Dot Com Investors Inc may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Dot Com Investors Inc does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Dot Com Investors Inc may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Dot Com Investors Inc may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Dot Com Investors Inc, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Dot Com Investors Inc will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Dot Com Investors Inc or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Dot Com Investors Inc; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Dot Com Investors Inc, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**  
The Dot Com Investors Inc website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Dot Com Investors Inc pages, or register with Dot Com Investors Inc site or services, a cookie helps Dot Com Investors Inc to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Dot Com Investors Inc website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Dot Com Investors Inc features that you customized.  
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Dot Com Investors Inc services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
Dot Com Investors Inc secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
Dot Com Investors Inc does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**  
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Dot Com Investors Inc by

**Contact us here:**  
– Web page: [www.invests.com](http://invests.com/)  
– Email: [legal@invests.com](mailto:legal@invests.com)  
– Telephone Number: +1 646 381 2130 Extension 1022

**Changes to this Statement**  
Dot Com Investors Inc will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Dot Com Investors Inc encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Dot Com Investors Inc is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**  
Dot Com Investors Inc welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Dot Com Investors Inc has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Dot Com Investors Inc at:

Dot Com Investors Inc  
8th Floor  
100 Church Street  
New York, New York 10007  
Email Address: [legal@invests.com](mailto:legal@invests.com)  
Telephone Number: +1 646 381 2130 Extension 1022

_Effective as of June 01, 2012_
